<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Remote Learning on AtNum</title>
    <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Remote Learning on AtNum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2022 AtNum. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://At-Num.github.io/edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</guid>
      <description>Any experienced educator will tell you the main challenge we face is student motivation. That same educator will tell you the number one answer to this challenge is student choice.
We here at AtNum have been developing the software for the MeetUsHere project. This has required thousands of lines of code in more than 5 programming languages, endless testing and deployments.
How do we maintain personal motivation?, by giving ourselves a chance to work on something different that we enjoy in computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lex&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</guid>
      <description>Lex has worked as a Literature / Language teacher in both Brazil and the UK. He has an established role as a security architect mentor both to the wider community through conference appearances and to trainees at his company Sthenos Information Security Ltd.
Lex is bilingual in English and Portuguese and studied linguistics during his Bachelor of Arts. As a cross cultural educator he is fully aware of the communication barriers for bilingual students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigel&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</guid>
      <description>Nigel has 15+ years experience working in Tertiary and Higher education. Nigel completed the final year of his Education diploma under Adelaide University&amp;rsquo;s Distinguished Professor of Sociology Jerry Smoliz who was the architect of Australia’s multicultural policy.
On completion of his Mathematics degree he worked extensively as an engineering tutor with a focus on Computer Science and Electrical engineering. At this time he won a junior lecturing position in a matriculation department teaching mathematics and statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
