<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Remote Learning on AtNum</title>
    <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Remote Learning on AtNum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2022 AtNum. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://At-Num.github.io/edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</guid>
      <description>Our motivation at AtNum for the development of Remote Learning Solutions is to add both Simplicity and Security simultaneously with ease of access. Every learning institution will have unique requirements but all will struggle with the above.
Here at AtNum we are actively researching emerging remote learning solutions and technologies. Having worked extensively in secondary and tertiary education as well as software engineering we feel we have the background to speak authentically on this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtNum Content Creator</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/content-creator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/content-creator/</guid>
      <description>Atnum Content Creator is a simple and easy to set up tool for creating educational screencasts. You can easily stream these screencasts from the cloud, one possibility is to stream your content from meetushere
Content Creator is free and easy to set up, will run on old computers. The video below will;
shows uses cases runs a demo outlines legal compliance with the license (so free to share and use) shows the Remote Learning ecosystem wrt Content Creator introduces Lecture Studio and BigBlueButton introduces meetushere and how to use it with Content Creator introduces AtNum see download and install below to access Content Creator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lex&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</guid>
      <description>Lex has worked as a Literature / Language teacher in both Brazil and the UK. He has an established role as a security architect mentor both to the wider community through conference appearances and to trainees at his company Sthenos Information Security Ltd.
Lex is bilingual in English and Portuguese and studied linguistics during his Bachelor of Arts. As a cross cultural educator he is fully aware of the communication barriers for bilingual students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigel&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</guid>
      <description>Nigel has 15+ years experience working in Tertiary and Higher education. Nigel completed the final year of his Education diploma under Adelaide University&amp;rsquo;s Distinguished Professor of Sociology Jerry Smoliz who was the architect of Australia’s multicultural policy.
On completion of his Mathematics degree he worked extensively as an engineering tutor with a focus on Computer Science and Electrical engineering. At this time he won a junior lecturing position in a matriculation department teaching mathematics and statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
