<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>AtNum</title>
    <link>https://At-Num.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AtNum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2022 AtNum. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:48:30 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://At-Num.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/motivation/</guid>
      <description>Our motivation at AtNum for the development of Remote Learning Solutions is to add both Simplicity and Security simultaneously with ease of access. Every learning institution will have unique requirements but all will struggle with the above.
Here at AtNum we are actively researching emerging remote learning solutions and technologies. Having worked extensively in secondary and tertiary education as well as software engineering we feel we have the background to speak authentically on this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtNum Content Creator</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/content-creator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/content-creator/</guid>
      <description>Atnum Content Creator is a simple and easy to set up tool for creating educational screencasts. You can easily stream these screencasts from the cloud, one possibility is to stream your content from meetushere
Content Creator is free and easy to set up, will run on old computers. The video below will;
shows uses cases runs a demo outlines legal compliance with the license (so free to share and use) shows the Remote Learning ecosystem wrt Content Creator introduces Lecture Studio and BigBlueButton introduces meetushere and how to use it with Content Creator introduces AtNum see download and install below to access Content Creator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lex&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/lex_teaching_background/</guid>
      <description>Lex has worked as a Literature / Language teacher in both Brazil and the UK. He has an established role as a security architect mentor both to the wider community through conference appearances and to trainees at his company Sthenos Information Security Ltd.
Lex is bilingual in English and Portuguese and studied linguistics during his Bachelor of Arts. As a cross cultural educator he is fully aware of the communication barriers for bilingual students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigel&#39;s teaching story</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/edu/nigels_background/</guid>
      <description>Nigel has 15+ years experience working in Tertiary and Higher education. Nigel completed the final year of his Education diploma under Adelaide University&amp;rsquo;s Distinguished Professor of Sociology Jerry Smoliz who was the architect of Australia’s multicultural policy.
On completion of his Mathematics degree he worked extensively as an engineering tutor with a focus on Computer Science and Electrical engineering. At this time he won a junior lecturing position in a matriculation department teaching mathematics and statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetushere Promotions</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/remote/promotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:48:30 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/remote/promotions/</guid>
      <description>Meetushere Promo Code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetushere</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/remote/meetushere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 23:48:30 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/remote/meetushere/</guid>
      <description>Announcing Meetushere</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:52:59 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/support/</guid>
      <description>Customer Support Policy We seek to provide opportunities for our customers to:
provide feedback report abuse request support contact support: support@atnum.uk Complaints procedure We take customer service very seriously. If, for any reason, you’re not happy with a product or the service you have received from us, we would really appreciate the opportunity to help makes things right. Talk to us.
Refunds Please refer to our refunds policy
FAQs All the latest information and answers to your frequently asked questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Statement</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 18:44:45 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/mission/</guid>
      <description>In Brief AtNum&amp;rsquo;s mission is to provide Cloud based services utilizing the latest technology and designs. We have a focus for secure remote learning.
By creating platforms and tools for facilitators we hope to realize homo faber.
Mission Secure Web tools for remote learning -&amp;gt; meetushere Secure In house tools for remote learning -&amp;gt; AtNum Content Creator Consult and train for remote learning and security Consult and develop for secure applications Vision empowering people via the use of tools homo faber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refunds</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 18:22:15 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/refunds/</guid>
      <description>Refunds Policy AtNum&amp;rsquo;s Meet Us Here is a video conferencing service. Your payments are made to the meeting host. AtNum takes a commision of your payment to the host. Video conferencing as a product will fall under the purview of the Consumer Rights Act as it pertains to digital content. Your rights as a consumer of digital content are enumerated here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 18:07:11 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions of Service Thank you for visiting AtNum’s Terms and Conditions of Service (the “Terms and Conditions”). These Terms and Conditions affect your legal rights; please read them carefully. These Terms and Conditions are an agreement between you and AtNum. Along with our representatives, officers, managers, members, subsidiaries, affiliates, parent companies, employees, and agents (collectively “AtNum” or “we” or “us” or “our”), we maintain the website at meetushere.com. These Terms and Conditions govern your use of the meetushere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 23:25:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/policies/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>AtNum Privacy Policy Protecting your privacy. Improving your online experience. Your trust is very important to us. At no time do we sell, aggregate or in any other way seek to gain in any commercial way from any information you provide to us. We do not use cookies. In fact, we pride ourselves on the stateless design of our applications. We are a security and application video conference consultancy firm for cloud enterprise applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-loadbalancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 23:53:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-loadbalancer/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure TLS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI Certificate Authority (CA)</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-cert-auth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 23:48:30 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-cert-auth/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure TLS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI Dynamic Groups vs AWS STS</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-dynamic-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 20:19:49 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/oci-dynamic-groups/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure IAM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Wireguard OCI</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/ubunt-wireguard-oci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:34:28 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/ubunt-wireguard-oci/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Ubuntu Wireguard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu on OCI</title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/ubunt-oci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 18:08:51 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/posts/development/ubunt-oci/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Ubuntu Image Iptables</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>What is AtNum? AtNum Ltd is a company that helps the enterprise make secure cloud applications with a focus on remote learning via video conferencing and creating tools for educators, however, AtNum takes a genuinely polyglot approach to creating and maintaining secure applications.
Take a moment to read our mission statement.
If you want to know more about the technical details, then please contact us. If you want to know more about AtNum&amp;rsquo;s work, then keep reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/consult/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/consult/</guid>
      <description>Consult Cloud Solutions Certified Oracle Architect and Application Developer 10+ years experience with AWS, GCP Cloud infrastructure specialists Cloud native specialists Application Development Golang, Kotlin, Javascript prefered System development on linux and windows Postgres and Oracle database Security Expertise Executive Consultancy Cyber Security Operations Risk Management Compliance Readiness Security Testing &amp;amp; Monitoring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://At-Num.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@atnum.uk (AtNum)</author>
      <guid>https://At-Num.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us Company Information AtNum Ltd is Scotland-based company, registered at Hudson House, 8 Albany Street, Edinburgh, EH1 3QB, under the Company No. SC659362
Our Application and Security experts are here to help.
Contact us at info@atnum.uk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
